var mcqs=[
  {
    category: "Music",
    id: "6266bc31b0e62e469cf43e8d",
    correctAnswer: "Percussion",
    options: [ "Percussion","Woodwind", "Brass", "Stringed"],
    question: "What type of instrument is a maraca?",
    tags: ["music"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "medium",
    regions: [],
    isNiche: false,
  },
  {
    category: "Music",
    id: "622a1c357cc59eab6f94ff10",
    correctAnswer: "Madonna",
    options: ["Eric Clapton",  "Madonna","Nicki Minaj", "Alanis Morissette"],
    question:
      "Which American singer and songwriter released the song 'Like a Virgin'?",
    tags: ["songs", "musicians", "general_knowledge", "1980's", "music"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "easy",
    regions: [],
    isNiche: false,
  },
  {
    category: "Music",
    id: "622a1c367cc59eab6f950324",
    correctAnswer: "Robert Smith",
    options: ["Thomas Lawrence", "John Martin", "Jack Austin","Robert Smith"],
    question: "Who was the lead singer of the Cure?",
    tags: ["music"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "medium",
    regions: [],
    isNiche: false,
  },
  {
    category: "Science",
    id: "624333a7cfaae40c129613f6",
    correctAnswer: "A Bitch",
    options: ["A Jill", "A Gander", "A Tigeress", "A Bitch"],
    question: "What is the word for a female dog?",
    tags: ["science"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "easy",
    regions: [],
    isNiche: false,
  },
  {
    category: "Sport & Leisure",
    id: "62417ccb8c3137686862d73b",
    correctAnswer: "Boston Red Sox",
    options: ["Boston United", "Boston Pirates", "Boston Inter","Boston Red Sox"],
    question: "Which of these is a baseball team based in Boston?",
    tags: ["baseball", "nba", "usa", "sport"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "easy",
    regions: [],
    isNiche: false,
  },
  {
    category: "Music",
    id: "622a1c397cc59eab6f950bde",
    correctAnswer: "Scorpions",
    options: ["Rammstein", "Sodom", "U.D.O.","Scorpions"],
    question: "Which German rock band released the song 'Still Loving You'?",
    tags: ["rock_music", "music"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "hard",
    regions: [],
    isNiche: false,
  },
  {
    category: "Film & TV",
    id: "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f8c0",
    correctAnswer: "Sigourney Weaver",
    options: ["Anne Bancroft", "Angela Lansbury", "Katharine Hepburn","Sigourney Weaver"],
    question: "Which actress played the role of Ellen Ripley in Alien?",
    tags: ["cult_films", "film", "acting", "film_and_tv"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "medium",
    regions: [],
    isNiche: false,
  },
  {
    category: "History",
    id: "622a1c367cc59eab6f9503fb",
    correctAnswer: "Chicago",
    options: ["Denver", "Dallas",  "Chicago","Seattle"],
    question:
      "The St. Valentine's Day massacre took place in this which city? ",
    tags: ["history"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "hard",
    regions: [],
    isNiche: false,
  },
  {
    category: "Film & TV",
    id: "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fb26",
    correctAnswer: "Louise Fletcher",
    options: ["Louise Fletcher","Isabelle Adjani", "Ann-Margret", "Glenda Jackson"],
    question:
      "Who won the 1975 Academy Award for Best Leading Actress for playing the role of Nurse Mildred Ratched in One Flew over the Cuckoo's Nest?",
    tags: ["acting", "academy_awards", "film", "film_and_tv"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "hard",
    regions: [],
    isNiche: false,
  },
  {
    category: "Food & Drink",
    id: "622a1c367cc59eab6f95027b",
    correctAnswer: "Greece ",
    options: ["Italy","Greece ","Switzerland", "Croatia"],
    question: "Where Might You Drink The Wine Retsina?",
    tags: ["food_and_drink"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "hard",
    regions: [],
    isNiche: false,
  },
];
// https://the-trivia-api.com/api/questions/